netlynx.org 2006-08-21

# Netlynx Technologies » Domain Name Registration and Web Hosting Mumbai India

**Netlynx Technologies Privacy Statement Information**   
Netlynx Technologies knows the importance of keeping your information private. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy, which embodies our commitment to the protection of your privacy through adherence to fair electronic information practices. This notice describes our privacy policy. By interacting with Netlynx Technologies, you agree to accept the guidelines described in this Privacy Statement.

**Information collected by Netlynx Technologies**  
Here are the types of information we gather from Netlynx Technologies's visitors:

Information entered on our website or given to us in any way are collected and stored in our system. Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers ("ICANN"), an organization that assumes responsible for domain name allocation, requires information about you during the domain name registration process. The information includes: name, address, phone number, email address and fax. When you register a domain name with Netlynx Technologies, we require you to provide credit card number and billing address. Financial information such as the above is collected during the domain name registration process. 

**How the information is shared:  
**It is required by ICANN that your name, address, phone number, email address and fax together with the creation and expiration dates of your domain name registration and the nameserver information associated with your domain name, be made available to the public via an interactive Web page and a "port 43" WHOIS service. Please note that Netlynx Technologies may not be able to control how members of the public may use the Whois information. 

**Sites Other than Netlynx Technologies  
**Netlynx Technologies will not be responsible for content or privacy policies of other Web Sites such as advertisers we may link to or those which link to our site. This Privacy Statement is only responsible for the information collected on Netlynx Technologies's site. 

**Cookies**  
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Netlynx Technologies to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Netlynx Technologies does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**  
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Netlynx Technologies and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Netlynx Technologies have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email [webmaster](mailto:sales@netlynx.org) or Contact Us:

906, Unique Towers,  
Off S.V.Road,  
Goregaon (W),  
Mumbai, India - 400062  
Tel: +91-9870005533

**»** Direct Information Pvt. Ltd.  
**»** Rediff.com India Ltd  
**»** Jalaram Infotech  
**»** Logic Boxes
